<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>iceland on Jacob Proffer</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/series/iceland/</link><description>Recent content in iceland on Jacob Proffer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jacobproffer.com/series/iceland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Iceland Blog 07</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-07/</guid><description>After a quick breakfast at Reykjavik Lights on Monday morning, Myles and I checked out of the hotel. The drive to the airport, which is in Keflavik, took around forty minutes from the capital. Once at the Keflavik Airport, I refueled the car at a nearby gas station and returned it to the designated parking lot for Europcar. An employee then inspected the vehicle while I signed paperwork. Afterwards, the same man drove Myles and I to the entrance of the airport.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 06</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-06/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-06/</guid><description>Myles and I did not have a lot planned for the final day in Iceland. It was a lazy day. We slept in and had breakfast at the hotel at eight. The only item on our itinerary was to go to the movies in the afternoon. We wanted to watch Deadpool 2, which had just been released. To kill time, we drove out to the south east of Reykjavik. From Route 1, we took a right onto Road 417, which snakes around a beautiful volcanic landscape with mossy hills.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 05</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-05/</guid><description>First and foremost, I should mention that I travel light. For the past year of travel, even to Japan, I&amp;rsquo;ve packed one pair of pants to cut down on space in my backpack. But Iceland taught me a valuable lesson about how denim does not survive in a wet environment. It started with a hike up to a waterfall called Glymur. Myles and I started the hike at ten in the morning.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 04</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-04/</guid><description>The drive to Skaftafell, a wilderness area inside of Vatnajökull National Park, took over four hours. Myles and I got up early on Friday to make the day trip. After brunch at the hotel, we were on the road before seven. Past the main attractions in the south center of Iceland, it was a rare occasion to pass another vehicle on Route 1. Throughout the scenic two hundred mile drive, we had near constant views of distant mountains, waterfalls and cliffs.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 03</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-03/</guid><description>There were still plenty of sites to see in Iceland, far too many. Thursday was dedicated to locations that Myles and I wanted to see towards the north east of Reykjavik. We got up around seven and were on the road again by eight. Though unlike Wednesday, we would not spend much time on Route 1 but a road called Road 36. The road is the main route from Reykjavik to a national park called Þingvellir, which was the first stop listed on our itinerary.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 02</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-02/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-02/</guid><description>Wednesday was the most well-thought out and detailed day of the trip. It started with breakfast at the hotel at around seven thirty, with the goal to leave the hotel by eight. For the half-hour breakfast, I enjoyed three waffles, sausages and baked beans. The coffee was great with no sugar and the orange juice just sweet enough. There also was a wide range of pastry offered, including croissants. But I refrained from overeating, as Myles and I had a lot of ground to cover that day.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 01</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-01/</guid><description>The Boeing 757 touched down in Iceland around six thirty in the morning on Tuesday, May 15th. Off the plane, I was corralled towards the main terminal with the rest of the passengers. But unlike in Tokyo, Japan, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to immediately go through customs. I was able to link-up with Myles, my travel partner for the trip, near a small cafe in the airport. We attempted to get some coffee but all of the stores past security required an outgoing boarding pass.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 00</title><link>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-00/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-00/</guid><description>This is it. Tomorrow morning, I embark on a trip to Iceland with my best friend and co-worker, Myles Kedrowski. Though we will fly separate airlines, both of our flights should touch down in Keflavik on Tuesday morning around the same time. Myles is fortunate to have a direct flight from Minnesota, via Iceland Air. I get to enjoy three separate Delta flights, with multi-hour layovers, which starts with a flight from K.</description></item></channel></rss>