<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Jacob Proffer</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
        <description>Jacob Proffer is a Front-End Developer working at Elegant Seagulls in Marquette, Michigan.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 15:16:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>

        <item>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;I woke at around three in the morning. Through the window in the hotel room, I could see that the night life was still active down the block. A group of people crossed the street, off to the next hostess club or karaoke bar. A lone taxi cab weaved past them. An ambulance and firetruck were parked on a corner to their right with the sirens on but I couldn’t see what for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 06:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/2018/03/13/japan-blog-04.html
            </guid>
        </item>

        <item>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;It was dark when the train pulled out of Narita. I did not expect this. In my mind, I had hopes to make it to Shinjuku and locate my hotel before nightfall. But it gets dark in Japan earlier than back home. It was six in the evening but it felt much later. I followed the progress of the train on my phone through Google Maps as the train snaked through small towns and past open fields. ...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/2018/01/08/japan-blog-03.html
            </guid>
        </item>

        <item>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;Immigration is a strange place to be alone, especially if you don’t speak the native language. I remember walking into Narita’s immigration. There’s a large green sign above the entrance that reads, “Quarantine”. I’d never been through the immigration process before but I had an idea of what to expect. You fill out some paperwork, get your photo taken and your passport is reviewed. It’...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/2017/12/28/japan-blog-02.html
            </guid>
        </item>

        <item>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;6265 miles. That’s how far I had to travel to get to Tokyo, Japan. Thankfully, I managed to due so in comfort aboard an American Airlines Boeing 787 Dreamliner. The flight, spanning 13 hours and 15 minutes, took place on a Tuesday afternoon out of Chicago O’hare International Airport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember walking up to my designated gate, K5. The plane was about to reach the ...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/2017/12/12/japan-blog-01.html
            </guid>
        </item>

        <item>
            <description>
                &lt;p&gt;This is it. Tonight is my last full night within the United States, at least for the next week. As of Wednesday morning, I will touch down at Narita International Airport. Which, if you didn’t know, is in Tokyo, Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will technically be my second international venture. Though I personally consider it to be my first. I’ve been out of the country once before, m...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <guid>
                http://localhost:4000/2017/11/13/japan-blog-00.html
            </guid>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
