<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>travel on Jacob Proffer</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/categories/travel/</link><description>Recent content in travel on Jacob Proffer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jacobproffer.com/categories/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Japan Blog 09</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-09/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-09/</guid><description>This is it. Tomorrow morning, I embark on my second trip to Japan. For the next week, I&amp;rsquo;ll explore Osaka, Kyoto and Nara. Compared to Tokyo, I expect similarities but a much different experience. Primarily, I will be open to experiment with unfamiliar foods. At the top of my list is takoyaki, which is a ball-shaped Japanese snack. It&amp;rsquo;s typically filled with octopus. There&amp;rsquo;s also kushikatsu, which is basically fried food on a skewer.</description></item><item><title>Norway Blog 03</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-03/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-03/</guid><description>The ferry from Tørvikbygd to Jondal is a short but pleasant experience. With an average time of twenty minutes to cross, Myles and I were able to use the bathroom, take pictures and even grab food from the onboard deli. The only downside is that the ferry crosses once per hour. We arrived early Sunday morning to an empty dock with a single employee present. Although patient, Myles and I were concerned that the delay would cost us sunlight.</description></item><item><title>Norway Blog 02</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-02/</guid><description>Norway has a lot of tunnels. The majority are short, between a half mile to a few miles long. There are a few that surpass ten with the longest being fifteen miles long. The length depends on the location and the span of the fjord. The majority of these tunnels are two lane, fully lit with emergency telephones. Yet there are also tunnels that are so narrow that only one vehicle can pass through at a time.</description></item><item><title>Norway Blog 01</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-01/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-01/</guid><description>I touched down in Norway to a sunny view of distant fjords, islands and a fleet of helicopters. It was nine in the morning, four hours before Myles was due to fly in. Since I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any luggage to claim, I bought a cup of coffee and relaxed in the main lounge. The Bergen airport is small in size, which left little to explore. But the nearby gates seemed to be busy.</description></item><item><title>Norway Blog 00</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/norway-blog-00/</guid><description>This is it. The final night before I commence my trip to the beautiful country of Norway. For the next week, Myles Kedrowski and I will be staying in the city of Bergen. Similar to our venture to Iceland, Myles and I will fly separate flights but meet up at the airport. He should arrive a few hours after I do on Friday afternoon. Our itinerary consists of nearly non-stop hiking throughout the north and south west of Norway.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 07</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-07/</guid><description>After a quick breakfast at Reykjavik Lights on Monday morning, Myles and I checked out of the hotel. The drive to the airport, which is in Keflavik, took around forty minutes from the capital. Once at the Keflavik Airport, I refueled the car at a nearby gas station and returned it to the designated parking lot for Europcar. An employee then inspected the vehicle while I signed paperwork. Afterwards, the same man drove Myles and I to the entrance of the airport.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 06</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-06/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-06/</guid><description>Myles and I did not have a lot planned for the final day in Iceland. It was a lazy day. We slept in and had breakfast at the hotel at eight. The only item on our itinerary was to go to the movies in the afternoon. We wanted to watch Deadpool 2, which had just been released. To kill time, we drove out to the south east of Reykjavik. From Route 1, we took a right onto Road 417, which snakes around a beautiful volcanic landscape with mossy hills.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 05</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-05/</guid><description>First and foremost, I should mention that I travel light. For the past year of travel, even to Japan, I&amp;rsquo;ve packed one pair of pants to cut down on space in my backpack. But Iceland taught me a valuable lesson about how denim does not survive in a wet environment. It started with a hike up to a waterfall called Glymur. Myles and I started the hike at ten in the morning.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 04</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-04/</guid><description>The drive to Skaftafell, a wilderness area inside of Vatnajökull National Park, took over four hours. Myles and I got up early on Friday to make the day trip. After brunch at the hotel, we were on the road before seven. Past the main attractions in the south center of Iceland, it was a rare occasion to pass another vehicle on Route 1. Throughout the scenic two hundred mile drive, we had near constant views of distant mountains, waterfalls and cliffs.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 03</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-03/</guid><description>There were still plenty of sites to see in Iceland, far too many. Thursday was dedicated to locations that Myles and I wanted to see towards the north east of Reykjavik. We got up around seven and were on the road again by eight. Though unlike Wednesday, we would not spend much time on Route 1 but a road called Road 36. The road is the main route from Reykjavik to a national park called Þingvellir, which was the first stop listed on our itinerary.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 02</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-02/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-02/</guid><description>Wednesday was the most well-thought out and detailed day of the trip. It started with breakfast at the hotel at around seven thirty, with the goal to leave the hotel by eight. For the half-hour breakfast, I enjoyed three waffles, sausages and baked beans. The coffee was great with no sugar and the orange juice just sweet enough. There also was a wide range of pastry offered, including croissants. But I refrained from overeating, as Myles and I had a lot of ground to cover that day.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 01</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-01/</guid><description>The Boeing 757 touched down in Iceland around six thirty in the morning on Tuesday, May 15th. Off the plane, I was corralled towards the main terminal with the rest of the passengers. But unlike in Tokyo, Japan, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to immediately go through customs. I was able to link-up with Myles, my travel partner for the trip, near a small cafe in the airport. We attempted to get some coffee but all of the stores past security required an outgoing boarding pass.</description></item><item><title>Iceland Blog 00</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-00/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/iceland-blog-00/</guid><description>This is it. Tomorrow morning, I embark on a trip to Iceland with my best friend and co-worker, Myles Kedrowski. Though we will fly separate airlines, both of our flights should touch down in Keflavik on Tuesday morning around the same time. Myles is fortunate to have a direct flight from Minnesota, via Iceland Air. I get to enjoy three separate Delta flights, with multi-hour layovers, which starts with a flight from K.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 08</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-08/</guid><description>As much I hated to return the room key, I checked out of the Hotel Gracery on Monday morning around eight. I considered breakfast at the Bonsalute Kabuki on the ground floor on my way out but decided to head to the Shinjuku Station instead. Although my flight wasn&amp;rsquo;t until six at night, I wanted to have plenty of time for the train ride, security and customs. I also planned to have a few hours to walk around the airport before the thirteen hour flight.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 07</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-07/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-07/</guid><description>For the final full day in Tokyo, Japan, I wanted to visit Ikebukuro for the Pokémon Center and revisit Akihabara. Which meant that it was going to be a long day. But I still made time for breakfast at the Bonsalute Kabuki. I mixed it up this time and try some noodles and white rice. But I also had potatoes and sausages with orange juice. Even though the food was delicious and it was a buffet, the restaurant was pricey at nearly three-thousand yen.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 06</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-06/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-06/</guid><description>Saturday in Tokyo was unique. I slept in for once, which provided an opportunity to seek breakfast somewhere other than Burger King. I tried out the breakfast buffet at the Bonsalute Kabuki, which was located on the ground floor of the hotel. The restaurant served Italian food throughout the day. But in the morning, there was a choice of Western or Japanese breakfast foods. I enjoyed a meal of potatoes, sausages and croissants with second helpings.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 05</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-05/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-05/</guid><description>Friday morning, I was out the door by seven. Breakfast was at Burger King, my new usual spot in Shinjuku. It was cheap, familiar and no one bothered me. I finished my food and walked over to Shinjuku Station, where I attempted to use one of the JR Line ticket booths. There was an English translation but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out what ticket I needed. Thankfully, there was a service center.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 04</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-04/</guid><description>I woke around three in the morning. Through the window in the hotel room, I could see that the night life was still active down the block. A group of people crossed the street, off to a hostess club or karaoke bar. A lone taxi cab weaved past them. An ambulance and firetruck were parked on a corner to their right with the sirens on but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see what for.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 03</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-03/</guid><description>It was dark when the train pulled out of Narita. I did not expect this. In my mind, I had hopes to make it to Shinjuku and locate my hotel before nightfall. But it gets dark in Japan earlier than back home. It was six in the evening but it felt much later. I followed the progress of the train on my phone through Google Maps as the train snaked through small towns and past open fields.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 02</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-02/</guid><description>Immigration is a strange place to be alone, especially if you don&amp;rsquo;t speak the native language. I remember walking into Narita&amp;rsquo;s immigration. There&amp;rsquo;s a large green sign above the entrance that reads, &amp;ldquo;Quarantine&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;d never been through the immigration process before but I had an idea of what to expect. You fill out some paperwork, get your photo taken and your passport is reviewed. It&amp;rsquo;s simple. The strange part was that everyone around me spoke a foreign language.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 01</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-01/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-01/</guid><description>6265 miles. That&amp;rsquo;s how far I had to travel to get to Tokyo, Japan. Thankfully, I managed to due so in comfort aboard an American Airlines Boeing 787 Dreamliner. The flight, spanning 13 hours and 15 minutes, took place on a Tuesday afternoon out of Chicago O&amp;rsquo;hare International Airport.
I remember walking up to my designated gate, K5. The plane was about to reach the jet bridge as I took a seat in the lounge.</description></item><item><title>Japan Blog 00</title><link>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-00/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://jacobproffer.com/travel/japan-blog-00/</guid><description>This is it. Tonight is my last full night within the United States, at least for the next week. As of Wednesday morning, I will touch down at Narita International Airport. Which, if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, is in Tokyo, Japan.
This will technically be my second international venture. Though I personally consider it to be my first. I&amp;rsquo;ve been out of the country once before, many years ago. My dad took me fishing in Canada, back before you were required to have a passport.</description></item></channel></rss>